SHANE CHRISTIE

WEBSITE DEVELOPER



786-618-2301

ShaneAzaniaChristie@gmail.com

West Palm Beach, Fl

dev.ShaneAzania.com
GitHub.com/ShaneAzania

PROFILE

A self motivated web developer with experience in Front End and Back End Development frameworks, strong creative and problem solving skills, team player mentality, an eye for detail, with the will and urge to learn any and everything needed to become a great team asset.

SKILLS

- Front End Web Development
- · React, Redux, & Context
- · Javascript, CSS, HTML
- SASS
- Python, Django, and Flask
- MySQL
- Firebase (noSQL)
- Git Hub
- Web Master

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING BOOTCAMP

CODING DOJO 2022

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS

FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY 2020 - 2022

EXPERIENCE

WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

seVIIn Threads | https://seviin-threads.netlify.app/

2022 - Present

- E-commerce Full Stack Developer
- Utilizing React, Redux, JavaScript, Google Firebase (noSQL),
 Google User Authentication, Styled javascript components, SASS and Bootstrap

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

PALM BEACH COUNTY SCHOOL DISTRICT

2022 - Present

- Technology troubleshooting, problem solving, management and installation
- Active Directory administrative duties
- Student management

WEB MASTER AND BUILDER

CIIITY MEDIA | ciiitymedia.com

2017 - 2022

- Increased online interactions and media presence by building website on Wordpress for CMS
- Broadened the reach and ease of access for online customers, and increasing sales by including e-commerce functionality and social multi platform store integration